d5creation.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy » D5 Creation

D5 Creation has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**A. Information Collected During Your Use of the D5 Creation Service.**  
In order to register, users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records.

If you decide to purchase any D5 Creation products or services, D5 Creation will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address (“Financial Information”). Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for [other purposes](https://www.2checkout.com/privacy/). D5 Creation does not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with its Solutions. Here it is mentioned that D5 Creation are not collecting or recording these information directly. We are using secure 2Checkout (www.2checkout.com) payment method. 2Checkout is a world leading payment gateway and follows their standard [Privacy Policy](https://www.2checkout.com/privacy/) accepted by millions of users worldwide.

**B. Our Use of Your Information  **  
We use customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about D5 Creation and promotional material from some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and us from fraud.

**C. Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

D5 Creation will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business’ personally identifiable information to any third party.

**D. Security**  
In order to maximize the protection of your information, D5 Creation Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, the payment gateway 2CHECKOUT uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet.  We will ensure your privacy of your information but if any disaster occurred, or something happened which is out of our control, D5 Creation will not be liable.

**E. General  **  
This Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the D5 Creation Agreement. D5 Creation reserves the right to change or modify this policy any time without any prior notice.

If you have any questions about this Policy or the practices of this site, please [Contact Us](http://d5creation.com/contact/).
